SHARATH **KUMAR**

GRAPHIC DESIGNER



sharathsnk@gmail.com



+91 7418765114 / +91 8072773471



sharathgraphicworks.com



About Me

Experienced Graphic Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the field of marketing and advertising. Skilled in Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After effects, Adobe Premiere Pro and Adobe Photoshop. Strong arts and design professional with a PGD focused in Multimedia Technology from ICAT Design And Media College.



Education

ICAT Design and Media College

2017

PGD Multimedia Technology Chennai

Dhanalakshmi College Of Engineering 2016

B.E. Electronics And Communication Chennai



☆ Soft Skills

A Hard Skills

Communication Collaboration Team work Leadership Flexiblity & Adaptability

Graphic Design Branding **Data Visualisation Project Planning** Research



X Tools Known



Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Premiere Pro Adobe Aftereffects Adobe Indesign MS Office Wix Website Builder Wordpress

Tamil **English**

Hobbies

Movies Video Games Cartoons

Experience

Digital Marketing Designer / Project Lead, 2 Years

(Jan 2018 - Jan 2020) Valued Epistemics Pvt. Ltd, Chennai. India.

Graphic Designer, 5 months

(June 2017 - Oct 2017) Untitled Solutions Provider. Chennai. India.



Project

Video Lesson Development

(Mar 2019 - Jan 2020) Valued Epistemics Pvt. Ltd, Chennai. India.

The purpose of the video lesson project is to develop the video lessons, which will help students to watch, learn & understand the concepts in a simple visual form

GRE Score Predictor

(Sep 2018 - Oct 2018) Valued Epistemics Pvt. Ltd, Chennai. India.

GRE Score Predictor is an application that will ask the student to take 20 minute long test where the results will be analyzed and predicted with high accuracy in a minute of time.